Luna Yu

UXUI DESIGNER

WEBSITE DEVELOPER

INTERIOR DESIGNER

BRIEF SUMMERY

Solution-focused and team-oriented with over 3 years of experience in user research and . Solely execute a project from conception to execution. Committed to continuous learning and aligning with team objectives. Strong creative and analytical skills. Basic proficiency in Canadian taxation.

WORK EXPERIENCE



Senior Brand Strategist assistant GUAGUA International design office, a

start-up creative design studio that specializes in reaching online audiences

@Beijing

January 2022 to August 2022 (8 months)

- Conceptualized brand identity and created multiple graphic style for company brochure.
- Improved and Boosted Brand's image by developing new ideas and engaging in professional networking to support outreach.
- Work closely with all stakeholders to create and maintain design materials for presentation and client meeting.
- Build and optimaze the circle path for internal design workflow.

Senior interior design project leader GUAGUA International design office

@Beijing

August 2021 to August 2022 (1 year)

- Complete independently 2-3 commercial projects; solve problems and generate solution for client
- Proficiency in Visual Work. Online internal coordination of communications among client, the marketing team and company leadership

LinkedIn Profile
https://www.linkedin.com/in/luna-yu-278014152/

LunaYu@cmail.carleton.ca +514-662-6488 Ottawa, Riverside

Click here for my portfolio

SKILLS

Adobe design set Videography

Figma HTML/ CSS UX research

Web design Project management tools

Visual communication Problem-Solving

Team collaboration C++

LANGUAGE

English (Preference)

French (Conversation)

Mandarin (Native)

EDUCATION HISTORY

VOLUNTEER WORK AND INTERESTS



Bachelor of Information Technology

Carleton University | 2021

• Specialized in Interactive media design

Diploma of Interior decorating and visual design

Lester. B. Pearson School board | 2019

- Cum Laude
- 2019 Outstanding student award



Volunteer, Income tax assistant, 2020-2023

Interests, Ilustration, Japanese, character design, self-developmemt

SCHOOL PROJECTS(IT-RELATED)



LITTLE KINDLE Project

Teamwork

Leader

Web design

UI&UX design

Multi-user, non-profit art marketplace for child artists. @Algonquin College November 2022

- Led cross-functional team in delivering website project, spearheading all decision making and visual interface design oversight.
- Utilized Figma for collaborative user research, ideation, and design.
- Adept in Design Thinking principles to drive user-centered solutions and streamline the design process.

MyFirstBank Web development

Independent

Web development

Html/css

Financial education and success-focused website for kids. @Algonquin College February 2023

- Successfully executed a full-cycle website development project for a simulated client, including conceptualization, design, and programming.
- Demonstrated proficiency in HTML and CSS, resulting in a polished and functional end product.